{"problemsArray": [
  {"answer": "x \u003c\u003d 12", "explanation": "We want to get x by itself on one side of the inequality.\nUse addition to remove the constant.\n-14x - 2 + 2 \u003e\u003d -170 + 2\nNext, use the division to remove the coefficient\nRemember to switch the inequality because the coefficient is negative\n(-14x)/-14 \u003c\u003d -168/-14\n", "question": "Solve the inequality for x:\n-14x - 2 \u003e\u003d -170", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x \u003e 9", "explanation": "We want to get x by itself on one side of the inequality.\nUse addition to remove the constant.\n2x - 7 + 7 \u003e 11 + 7\nNext, use division to remove the coefficient.\n(2x)/2 \u003e 18/2\n", "question": "Solve the inequality for x:\n2x - 7 \u003e 11", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x \u003c 11", "explanation": "We want to get x by itself on one side of the inequality.\nUse addition to remove the constant.\n14x + 2 - 2 \u003c 156 - 2\nNext, use division to remove the coefficient.\n(14x)/14 \u003c 154/14\n", "question": "Solve the inequality for x:\n14x + 2 \u003c 156", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x \u003c\u003d -13", "explanation": "We want to get x by itself on one side of the inequality.\nUse addition to remove the constant.\n15x - 12 + 12 \u003c\u003d -207 + 12\nNext, use division to remove the coefficient.\n(15x)/15 \u003c\u003d -195/15\n", "question": "Solve the inequality for x:\n15x - 12 \u003c\u003d -207", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x \u003c 7", "explanation": "We want to get x by itself on one side of the inequality.\nUse addition to remove the constant.\n6x + 6 - 6 \u003c 48 - 6\nNext, use division to remove the coefficient.\n(6x)/6 \u003c 42/6\n", "question": "Solve the inequality for x:\n6x + 6 \u003c 48", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x \u003e 10", "explanation": "We want to get x by itself on one side of the inequality.\nUse addition to remove the constant.\n2x + 7 - 7 \u003e 27 - 7\nNext, use division to remove the coefficient.\n(2x)/2 \u003e 20/2\n", "question": "Solve the inequality for x:\n2x + 7 \u003e 27", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x \u003e -1", "explanation": "We want to get x by itself on one side of the inequality.\nUse addition to remove the constant.\n15x - 14 + 14 \u003e -29 + 14\nNext, use division to remove the coefficient.\n(15x)/15 \u003e -15/15\n", "question": "Solve the inequality for x:\n15x - 14 \u003e -29", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x \u003e 11", "explanation": "We want to get x by itself on one side of the inequality.\nUse addition to remove the constant.\n-3x - 8 + 8 \u003c -41 + 8\nNext, use the division to remove the coefficient\nRemember to switch the inequality because the coefficient is negative\n(-3x)/-3 \u003e -33/-3\n", "question": "Solve the inequality for x:\n-3x - 8 \u003c -41", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x \u003e\u003d -4", "explanation": "We want to get x by itself on one side of the inequality.\nUse addition to remove the constant.\n-4x + 5 - 5 \u003c\u003d 21 - 5\nNext, use the division to remove the coefficient\nRemember to switch the inequality because the coefficient is negative\n(-4x)/-4 \u003e\u003d 16/-4\n", "question": "Solve the inequality for x:\n-4x + 5 \u003c\u003d 21", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x \u003c\u003d -9", "explanation": "We want to get x by itself on one side of the inequality.\nUse addition to remove the constant.\n4x + 7 - 7 \u003c\u003d -29 - 7\nNext, use division to remove the coefficient.\n(4x)/4 \u003c\u003d -36/4\n", "question": "Solve the inequality for x:\n4x + 7 \u003c\u003d -29", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x \u003c 3", "explanation": "We want to get x by itself on one side of the inequality.\nUse addition to remove the constant.\nx + 11 - 11 \u003c 14 - 11\n", "question": "Solve the inequality for x:\nx + 11 \u003c 14", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x \u003e\u003d -12", "explanation": "We want to get x by itself on one side of the inequality.\nUse addition to remove the constant.\n-8x + 4 - 4 \u003c\u003d 100 - 4\nNext, use the division to remove the coefficient\nRemember to switch the inequality because the coefficient is negative\n(-8x)/-8 \u003e\u003d 96/-8\n", "question": "Solve the inequality for x:\n-8x + 4 \u003c\u003d 100", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x \u003c\u003d 10", "explanation": "We want to get x by itself on one side of the inequality.\nUse addition to remove the constant.\n-x + 8 - 8 \u003e\u003d -2 - 8\nNext, use the division to remove the coefficient\nRemember to switch the inequality because the coefficient is negative\n(-x)/-1 \u003c\u003d -10/-1\n", "question": "Solve the inequality for x:\n-x + 8 \u003e\u003d -2", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x \u003c\u003d 10", "explanation": "We want to get x by itself on one side of the inequality.\nUse addition to remove the constant.\n4x + 4 - 4 \u003c\u003d 44 - 4\nNext, use division to remove the coefficient.\n(4x)/4 \u003c\u003d 40/4\n", "question": "Solve the inequality for x:\n4x + 4 \u003c\u003d 44", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x \u003e -10", "explanation": "We want to get x by itself on one side of the inequality.\nUse addition to remove the constant.\n-3x - 9 + 9 \u003c 21 + 9\nNext, use the division to remove the coefficient\nRemember to switch the inequality because the coefficient is negative\n(-3x)/-3 \u003e 30/-3\n", "question": "Solve the inequality for x:\n-3x - 9 \u003c 21", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x \u003e 7", "explanation": "We want to get x by itself on one side of the inequality.\nUse addition to remove the constant.\n4x + 7 - 7 \u003e 35 - 7\nNext, use division to remove the coefficient.\n(4x)/4 \u003e 28/4\n", "question": "Solve the inequality for x:\n4x + 7 \u003e 35", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x \u003c\u003d 3", "explanation": "We want to get x by itself on one side of the inequality.\nUse addition to remove the constant.\n7x + 14 - 14 \u003c\u003d 35 - 14\nNext, use division to remove the coefficient.\n(7x)/7 \u003c\u003d 21/7\n", "question": "Solve the inequality for x:\n7x + 14 \u003c\u003d 35", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x \u003e\u003d -1", "explanation": "We want to get x by itself on one side of the inequality.\nUse addition to remove the constant.\n2x - 3 + 3 \u003e\u003d -5 + 3\nNext, use division to remove the coefficient.\n(2x)/2 \u003e\u003d -2/2\n", "question": "Solve the inequality for x:\n2x - 3 \u003e\u003d -5", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x \u003c\u003d -4", "explanation": "We want to get x by itself on one side of the inequality.\nUse addition to remove the constant.\n15x - 11 + 11 \u003c\u003d -71 + 11\nNext, use division to remove the coefficient.\n(15x)/15 \u003c\u003d -60/15\n", "question": "Solve the inequality for x:\n15x - 11 \u003c\u003d -71", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x \u003c 5", "explanation": "We want to get x by itself on one side of the inequality.\nUse addition to remove the constant.\n2x + 15 - 15 \u003c 25 - 15\nNext, use division to remove the coefficient.\n(2x)/2 \u003c 10/2\n", "question": "Solve the inequality for x:\n2x + 15 \u003c 25", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x \u003e -3", "explanation": "We want to get x by itself on one side of the inequality.\nUse addition to remove the constant.\n4x + 3 - 3 \u003e -9 - 3\nNext, use division to remove the coefficient.\n(4x)/4 \u003e -12/4\n", "question": "Solve the inequality for x:\n4x + 3 \u003e -9", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x \u003e\u003d 8", "explanation": "We want to get x by itself on one side of the inequality.\nUse addition to remove the constant.\n9x - 15 + 15 \u003e\u003d 57 + 15\nNext, use division to remove the coefficient.\n(9x)/9 \u003e\u003d 72/9\n", "question": "Solve the inequality for x:\n9x - 15 \u003e\u003d 57", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x \u003c 1", "explanation": "We want to get x by itself on one side of the inequality.\nUse addition to remove the constant.\n3x + 4 - 4 \u003c 7 - 4\nNext, use division to remove the coefficient.\n(3x)/3 \u003c 3/3\n", "question": "Solve the inequality for x:\n3x + 4 \u003c 7", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x \u003e\u003d -9", "explanation": "We want to get x by itself on one side of the inequality.\nUse addition to remove the constant.\n12x - 3 + 3 \u003e\u003d -111 + 3\nNext, use division to remove the coefficient.\n(12x)/12 \u003e\u003d -108/12\n", "question": "Solve the inequality for x:\n12x - 3 \u003e\u003d -111", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x \u003c\u003d -6", "explanation": "We want to get x by itself on one side of the inequality.\nUse addition to remove the constant.\n15x + 9 - 9 \u003c\u003d -81 - 9\nNext, use division to remove the coefficient.\n(15x)/15 \u003c\u003d -90/15\n", "question": "Solve the inequality for x:\n15x + 9 \u003c\u003d -81", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x \u003c -4", "explanation": "We want to get x by itself on one side of the inequality.\nUse addition to remove the constant.\n-12x + 7 - 7 \u003e 55 - 7\nNext, use the division to remove the coefficient\nRemember to switch the inequality because the coefficient is negative\n(-12x)/-12 \u003c 48/-12\n", "question": "Solve the inequality for x:\n-12x + 7 \u003e 55", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x \u003e 3", "explanation": "We want to get x by itself on one side of the inequality.\nUse addition to remove the constant.\n12x + 2 - 2 \u003e 38 - 2\nNext, use division to remove the coefficient.\n(12x)/12 \u003e 36/12\n", "question": "Solve the inequality for x:\n12x + 2 \u003e 38", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x \u003e\u003d -5", "explanation": "We want to get x by itself on one side of the inequality.\nUse addition to remove the constant.\n7x - 3 + 3 \u003e\u003d -38 + 3\nNext, use division to remove the coefficient.\n(7x)/7 \u003e\u003d -35/7\n", "question": "Solve the inequality for x:\n7x - 3 \u003e\u003d -38", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x \u003c\u003d 6", "explanation": "We want to get x by itself on one side of the inequality.\nUse addition to remove the constant.\n8x + 2 - 2 \u003c\u003d 50 - 2\nNext, use division to remove the coefficient.\n(8x)/8 \u003c\u003d 48/8\n", "question": "Solve the inequality for x:\n8x + 2 \u003c\u003d 50", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x \u003c 3", "explanation": "We want to get x by itself on one side of the inequality.\nUse addition to remove the constant.\n7x + 1 - 1 \u003c 22 - 1\nNext, use division to remove the coefficient.\n(7x)/7 \u003c 21/7\n", "question": "Solve the inequality for x:\n7x + 1 \u003c 22", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x \u003e\u003d -12", "explanation": "We want to get x by itself on one side of the inequality.\nUse addition to remove the constant.\n-3x + 5 - 5 \u003c\u003d 41 - 5\nNext, use the division to remove the coefficient\nRemember to switch the inequality because the coefficient is negative\n(-3x)/-3 \u003e\u003d 36/-3\n", "question": "Solve the inequality for x:\n-3x + 5 \u003c\u003d 41", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x \u003e 8", "explanation": "We want to get x by itself on one side of the inequality.\nUse addition to remove the constant.\n12x + 8 - 8 \u003e 104 - 8\nNext, use division to remove the coefficient.\n(12x)/12 \u003e 96/12\n", "question": "Solve the inequality for x:\n12x + 8 \u003e 104", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x \u003e\u003d 6", "explanation": "We want to get x by itself on one side of the inequality.\nUse addition to remove the constant.\n-x + 3 - 3 \u003c\u003d -3 - 3\nNext, use the division to remove the coefficient\nRemember to switch the inequality because the coefficient is negative\n(-x)/-1 \u003e\u003d -6/-1\n", "question": "Solve the inequality for x:\n-x + 3 \u003c\u003d -3", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x \u003c\u003d 2", "explanation": "We want to get x by itself on one side of the inequality.\nUse addition to remove the constant.\n-9x - 0 \u003e\u003d -18 - 0\nNext, use the division to remove the coefficient\nRemember to switch the inequality because the coefficient is negative\n(-9x)/-9 \u003c\u003d -18/-9\n", "question": "Solve the inequality for x:\n-9x \u003e\u003d -18", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x \u003c\u003d 15", "explanation": "We want to get x by itself on one side of the inequality.\nUse addition to remove the constant.\n3x + 11 - 11 \u003c\u003d 56 - 11\nNext, use division to remove the coefficient.\n(3x)/3 \u003c\u003d 45/3\n", "question": "Solve the inequality for x:\n3x + 11 \u003c\u003d 56", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x \u003e\u003d 12", "explanation": "We want to get x by itself on one side of the inequality.\nUse addition to remove the constant.\n14x + 11 - 11 \u003e\u003d 179 - 11\nNext, use division to remove the coefficient.\n(14x)/14 \u003e\u003d 168/14\n", "question": "Solve the inequality for x:\n14x + 11 \u003e\u003d 179", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x \u003e\u003d 6", "explanation": "We want to get x by itself on one side of the inequality.\nUse addition to remove the constant.\n-4x + 1 - 1 \u003c\u003d -23 - 1\nNext, use the division to remove the coefficient\nRemember to switch the inequality because the coefficient is negative\n(-4x)/-4 \u003e\u003d -24/-4\n", "question": "Solve the inequality for x:\n-4x + 1 \u003c\u003d -23", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x \u003e -8", "explanation": "We want to get x by itself on one side of the inequality.\nUse addition to remove the constant.\n4x + 5 - 5 \u003e -27 - 5\nNext, use division to remove the coefficient.\n(4x)/4 \u003e -32/4\n", "question": "Solve the inequality for x:\n4x + 5 \u003e -27", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x \u003c\u003d -14", "explanation": "We want to get x by itself on one side of the inequality.\nUse addition to remove the constant.\n-4x - 7 + 7 \u003e\u003d 49 + 7\nNext, use the division to remove the coefficient\nRemember to switch the inequality because the coefficient is negative\n(-4x)/-4 \u003c\u003d 56/-4\n", "question": "Solve the inequality for x:\n-4x - 7 \u003e\u003d 49", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x \u003c 14", "explanation": "We want to get x by itself on one side of the inequality.\nUse addition to remove the constant.\n-x + 12 - 12 \u003e -2 - 12\nNext, use the division to remove the coefficient\nRemember to switch the inequality because the coefficient is negative\n(-x)/-1 \u003c -14/-1\n", "question": "Solve the inequality for x:\n-x + 12 \u003e -2", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x \u003c -6", "explanation": "We want to get x by itself on one side of the inequality.\nUse addition to remove the constant.\n-12x + 11 - 11 \u003e 83 - 11\nNext, use the division to remove the coefficient\nRemember to switch the inequality because the coefficient is negative\n(-12x)/-12 \u003c 72/-12\n", "question": "Solve the inequality for x:\n-12x + 11 \u003e 83", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x \u003e\u003d 5", "explanation": "We want to get x by itself on one side of the inequality.\nUse addition to remove the constant.\n4x + 5 - 5 \u003e\u003d 25 - 5\nNext, use division to remove the coefficient.\n(4x)/4 \u003e\u003d 20/4\n", "question": "Solve the inequality for x:\n4x + 5 \u003e\u003d 25", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x \u003e\u003d 7", "explanation": "We want to get x by itself on one side of the inequality.\nUse addition to remove the constant.\n3x + 3 - 3 \u003e\u003d 24 - 3\nNext, use division to remove the coefficient.\n(3x)/3 \u003e\u003d 21/3\n", "question": "Solve the inequality for x:\n3x + 3 \u003e\u003d 24", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x \u003c\u003d 14", "explanation": "We want to get x by itself on one side of the inequality.\nUse addition to remove the constant.\n-13x - 9 + 9 \u003e\u003d -191 + 9\nNext, use the division to remove the coefficient\nRemember to switch the inequality because the coefficient is negative\n(-13x)/-13 \u003c\u003d -182/-13\n", "question": "Solve the inequality for x:\n-13x - 9 \u003e\u003d -191", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x \u003e 2", "explanation": "We want to get x by itself on one side of the inequality.\nUse addition to remove the constant.\n15x + 14 - 14 \u003e 44 - 14\nNext, use division to remove the coefficient.\n(15x)/15 \u003e 30/15\n", "question": "Solve the inequality for x:\n15x + 14 \u003e 44", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x \u003c\u003d -1", "explanation": "We want to get x by itself on one side of the inequality.\nUse addition to remove the constant.\n-15x - 15 + 15 \u003e\u003d 0 + 15\nNext, use the division to remove the coefficient\nRemember to switch the inequality because the coefficient is negative\n(-15x)/-15 \u003c\u003d 15/-15\n", "question": "Solve the inequality for x:\n-15x - 15 \u003e\u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x \u003c 7", "explanation": "We want to get x by itself on one side of the inequality.\nUse addition to remove the constant.\n12x - 14 + 14 \u003c 70 + 14\nNext, use division to remove the coefficient.\n(12x)/12 \u003c 84/12\n", "question": "Solve the inequality for x:\n12x - 14 \u003c 70", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x \u003c 7", "explanation": "We want to get x by itself on one side of the inequality.\nUse addition to remove the constant.\n-8x - 2 + 2 \u003e -58 + 2\nNext, use the division to remove the coefficient\nRemember to switch the inequality because the coefficient is negative\n(-8x)/-8 \u003c -56/-8\n", "question": "Solve the inequality for x:\n-8x - 2 \u003e -58", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x \u003c\u003d 10", "explanation": "We want to get x by itself on one side of the inequality.\nUse addition to remove the constant.\n-11x + 5 - 5 \u003e\u003d -105 - 5\nNext, use the division to remove the coefficient\nRemember to switch the inequality because the coefficient is negative\n(-11x)/-11 \u003c\u003d -110/-11\n", "question": "Solve the inequality for x:\n-11x + 5 \u003e\u003d -105", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x \u003c 3", "explanation": "We want to get x by itself on one side of the inequality.\nUse addition to remove the constant.\n-3x - 6 + 6 \u003e -15 + 6\nNext, use the division to remove the coefficient\nRemember to switch the inequality because the coefficient is negative\n(-3x)/-3 \u003c -9/-3\n", "question": "Solve the inequality for x:\n-3x - 6 \u003e -15", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x \u003c -4", "explanation": "We want to get x by itself on one side of the inequality.\nUse addition to remove the constant.\n-x + 1 - 1 \u003e 5 - 1\nNext, use the division to remove the coefficient\nRemember to switch the inequality because the coefficient is negative\n(-x)/-1 \u003c 4/-1\n", "question": "Solve the inequality for x:\n-x + 1 \u003e 5", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x \u003e -2", "explanation": "We want to get x by itself on one side of the inequality.\nUse addition to remove the constant.\n12x + 1 - 1 \u003e -23 - 1\nNext, use division to remove the coefficient.\n(12x)/12 \u003e -24/12\n", "question": "Solve the inequality for x:\n12x + 1 \u003e -23", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x \u003c -9", "explanation": "We want to get x by itself on one side of the inequality.\nUse addition to remove the constant.\n11x + 15 - 15 \u003c -84 - 15\nNext, use division to remove the coefficient.\n(11x)/11 \u003c -99/11\n", "question": "Solve the inequality for x:\n11x + 15 \u003c -84", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x \u003e -15", "explanation": "We want to get x by itself on one side of the inequality.\nUse addition to remove the constant.\n7x - 9 + 9 \u003e -114 + 9\nNext, use division to remove the coefficient.\n(7x)/7 \u003e -105/7\n", "question": "Solve the inequality for x:\n7x - 9 \u003e -114", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x \u003e\u003d -6", "explanation": "We want to get x by itself on one side of the inequality.\nUse addition to remove the constant.\n7x - 13 + 13 \u003e\u003d -55 + 13\nNext, use division to remove the coefficient.\n(7x)/7 \u003e\u003d -42/7\n", "question": "Solve the inequality for x:\n7x - 13 \u003e\u003d -55", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x \u003e -5", "explanation": "We want to get x by itself on one side of the inequality.\nUse addition to remove the constant.\n-8x - 15 + 15 \u003c 25 + 15\nNext, use the division to remove the coefficient\nRemember to switch the inequality because the coefficient is negative\n(-8x)/-8 \u003e 40/-8\n", "question": "Solve the inequality for x:\n-8x - 15 \u003c 25", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x \u003e -3", "explanation": "We want to get x by itself on one side of the inequality.\nUse addition to remove the constant.\n-13x + 8 - 8 \u003c 47 - 8\nNext, use the division to remove the coefficient\nRemember to switch the inequality because the coefficient is negative\n(-13x)/-13 \u003e 39/-13\n", "question": "Solve the inequality for x:\n-13x + 8 \u003c 47", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x \u003c\u003d 14", "explanation": "We want to get x by itself on one side of the inequality.\nUse addition to remove the constant.\n10x + 10 - 10 \u003c\u003d 150 - 10\nNext, use division to remove the coefficient.\n(10x)/10 \u003c\u003d 140/10\n", "question": "Solve the inequality for x:\n10x + 10 \u003c\u003d 150", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x \u003e -2", "explanation": "We want to get x by itself on one side of the inequality.\nUse addition to remove the constant.\n8x + 11 - 11 \u003e -5 - 11\nNext, use division to remove the coefficient.\n(8x)/8 \u003e -16/8\n", "question": "Solve the inequality for x:\n8x + 11 \u003e -5", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x \u003c\u003d 2", "explanation": "We want to get x by itself on one side of the inequality.\nUse addition to remove the constant.\n-15x + 12 - 12 \u003e\u003d -18 - 12\nNext, use the division to remove the coefficient\nRemember to switch the inequality because the coefficient is negative\n(-15x)/-15 \u003c\u003d -30/-15\n", "question": "Solve the inequality for x:\n-15x + 12 \u003e\u003d -18", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x \u003e\u003d -6", "explanation": "We want to get x by itself on one side of the inequality.\nUse addition to remove the constant.\n15x + 4 - 4 \u003e\u003d -86 - 4\nNext, use division to remove the coefficient.\n(15x)/15 \u003e\u003d -90/15\n", "question": "Solve the inequality for x:\n15x + 4 \u003e\u003d -86", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x \u003c 5", "explanation": "We want to get x by itself on one side of the inequality.\nUse addition to remove the constant.\n10x - 7 + 7 \u003c 43 + 7\nNext, use division to remove the coefficient.\n(10x)/10 \u003c 50/10\n", "question": "Solve the inequality for x:\n10x - 7 \u003c 43", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x \u003e\u003d 5", "explanation": "We want to get x by itself on one side of the inequality.\nUse addition to remove the constant.\n12x + 13 - 13 \u003e\u003d 73 - 13\nNext, use division to remove the coefficient.\n(12x)/12 \u003e\u003d 60/12\n", "question": "Solve the inequality for x:\n12x + 13 \u003e\u003d 73", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x \u003c\u003d -11", "explanation": "We want to get x by itself on one side of the inequality.\nUse addition to remove the constant.\n-x + 6 - 6 \u003e\u003d 17 - 6\nNext, use the division to remove the coefficient\nRemember to switch the inequality because the coefficient is negative\n(-x)/-1 \u003c\u003d 11/-1\n", "question": "Solve the inequality for x:\n-x + 6 \u003e\u003d 17", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x \u003e\u003d -15", "explanation": "We want to get x by itself on one side of the inequality.\nUse addition to remove the constant.\n14x + 2 - 2 \u003e\u003d -208 - 2\nNext, use division to remove the coefficient.\n(14x)/14 \u003e\u003d -210/14\n", "question": "Solve the inequality for x:\n14x + 2 \u003e\u003d -208", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x \u003c 5", "explanation": "We want to get x by itself on one side of the inequality.\nUse addition to remove the constant.\n-5x + 11 - 11 \u003e -14 - 11\nNext, use the division to remove the coefficient\nRemember to switch the inequality because the coefficient is negative\n(-5x)/-5 \u003c -25/-5\n", "question": "Solve the inequality for x:\n-5x + 11 \u003e -14", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x \u003e\u003d -6", "explanation": "We want to get x by itself on one side of the inequality.\nUse addition to remove the constant.\n-8x + 6 - 6 \u003c\u003d 54 - 6\nNext, use the division to remove the coefficient\nRemember to switch the inequality because the coefficient is negative\n(-8x)/-8 \u003e\u003d 48/-8\n", "question": "Solve the inequality for x:\n-8x + 6 \u003c\u003d 54", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x \u003e 13", "explanation": "We want to get x by itself on one side of the inequality.\nUse addition to remove the constant.\n4x + 13 - 13 \u003e 65 - 13\nNext, use division to remove the coefficient.\n(4x)/4 \u003e 52/4\n", "question": "Solve the inequality for x:\n4x + 13 \u003e 65", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x \u003e\u003d 4", "explanation": "We want to get x by itself on one side of the inequality.\nUse addition to remove the constant.\n-8x + 6 - 6 \u003c\u003d -26 - 6\nNext, use the division to remove the coefficient\nRemember to switch the inequality because the coefficient is negative\n(-8x)/-8 \u003e\u003d -32/-8\n", "question": "Solve the inequality for x:\n-8x + 6 \u003c\u003d -26", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x \u003c\u003d 13", "explanation": "We want to get x by itself on one side of the inequality.\nUse addition to remove the constant.\n-13x - 2 + 2 \u003e\u003d -171 + 2\nNext, use the division to remove the coefficient\nRemember to switch the inequality because the coefficient is negative\n(-13x)/-13 \u003c\u003d -169/-13\n", "question": "Solve the inequality for x:\n-13x - 2 \u003e\u003d -171", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x \u003c 3", "explanation": "We want to get x by itself on one side of the inequality.\nUse addition to remove the constant.\n-7x + 6 - 6 \u003e -15 - 6\nNext, use the division to remove the coefficient\nRemember to switch the inequality because the coefficient is negative\n(-7x)/-7 \u003c -21/-7\n", "question": "Solve the inequality for x:\n-7x + 6 \u003e -15", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x \u003c -6", "explanation": "We want to get x by itself on one side of the inequality.\nUse addition to remove the constant.\n-x - 5 + 5 \u003e 1 + 5\nNext, use the division to remove the coefficient\nRemember to switch the inequality because the coefficient is negative\n(-x)/-1 \u003c 6/-1\n", "question": "Solve the inequality for x:\n-x - 5 \u003e 1", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x \u003e\u003d 14", "explanation": "We want to get x by itself on one side of the inequality.\nUse addition to remove the constant.\n15x + 5 - 5 \u003e\u003d 215 - 5\nNext, use division to remove the coefficient.\n(15x)/15 \u003e\u003d 210/15\n", "question": "Solve the inequality for x:\n15x + 5 \u003e\u003d 215", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x \u003e\u003d -4", "explanation": "We want to get x by itself on one side of the inequality.\nUse addition to remove the constant.\n-4x + 12 - 12 \u003c\u003d 28 - 12\nNext, use the division to remove the coefficient\nRemember to switch the inequality because the coefficient is negative\n(-4x)/-4 \u003e\u003d 16/-4\n", "question": "Solve the inequality for x:\n-4x + 12 \u003c\u003d 28", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x \u003e\u003d 9", "explanation": "We want to get x by itself on one side of the inequality.\nUse addition to remove the constant.\n-15x + 7 - 7 \u003c\u003d -128 - 7\nNext, use the division to remove the coefficient\nRemember to switch the inequality because the coefficient is negative\n(-15x)/-15 \u003e\u003d -135/-15\n", "question": "Solve the inequality for x:\n-15x + 7 \u003c\u003d -128", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x \u003c\u003d 10", "explanation": "We want to get x by itself on one side of the inequality.\nUse addition to remove the constant.\n10x + 7 - 7 \u003c\u003d 107 - 7\nNext, use division to remove the coefficient.\n(10x)/10 \u003c\u003d 100/10\n", "question": "Solve the inequality for x:\n10x + 7 \u003c\u003d 107", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x \u003c\u003d 12", "explanation": "We want to get x by itself on one side of the inequality.\nUse addition to remove the constant.\n-x + 3 - 3 \u003e\u003d -9 - 3\nNext, use the division to remove the coefficient\nRemember to switch the inequality because the coefficient is negative\n(-x)/-1 \u003c\u003d -12/-1\n", "question": "Solve the inequality for x:\n-x + 3 \u003e\u003d -9", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x \u003e -5", "explanation": "We want to get x by itself on one side of the inequality.\nUse addition to remove the constant.\n15x + 8 - 8 \u003e -67 - 8\nNext, use division to remove the coefficient.\n(15x)/15 \u003e -75/15\n", "question": "Solve the inequality for x:\n15x + 8 \u003e -67", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x \u003c 7", "explanation": "We want to get x by itself on one side of the inequality.\nUse addition to remove the constant.\n5x + 9 - 9 \u003c 44 - 9\nNext, use division to remove the coefficient.\n(5x)/5 \u003c 35/5\n", "question": "Solve the inequality for x:\n5x + 9 \u003c 44", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x \u003c\u003d -5", "explanation": "We want to get x by itself on one side of the inequality.\nUse addition to remove the constant.\n11x - 3 + 3 \u003c\u003d -58 + 3\nNext, use division to remove the coefficient.\n(11x)/11 \u003c\u003d -55/11\n", "question": "Solve the inequality for x:\n11x - 3 \u003c\u003d -58", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x \u003e\u003d 12", "explanation": "We want to get x by itself on one side of the inequality.\nUse addition to remove the constant.\n5x - 8 + 8 \u003e\u003d 52 + 8\nNext, use division to remove the coefficient.\n(5x)/5 \u003e\u003d 60/5\n", "question": "Solve the inequality for x:\n5x - 8 \u003e\u003d 52", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x \u003c 2", "explanation": "We want to get x by itself on one side of the inequality.\nUse addition to remove the constant.\n5x + 13 - 13 \u003c 23 - 13\nNext, use division to remove the coefficient.\n(5x)/5 \u003c 10/5\n", "question": "Solve the inequality for x:\n5x + 13 \u003c 23", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x \u003c -2", "explanation": "We want to get x by itself on one side of the inequality.\nUse addition to remove the constant.\n5x + 1 - 1 \u003c -9 - 1\nNext, use division to remove the coefficient.\n(5x)/5 \u003c -10/5\n", "question": "Solve the inequality for x:\n5x + 1 \u003c -9", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x \u003e 3", "explanation": "We want to get x by itself on one side of the inequality.\nUse addition to remove the constant.\n10x - 12 + 12 \u003e 18 + 12\nNext, use division to remove the coefficient.\n(10x)/10 \u003e 30/10\n", "question": "Solve the inequality for x:\n10x - 12 \u003e 18", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x \u003e\u003d 10", "explanation": "We want to get x by itself on one side of the inequality.\nUse addition to remove the constant.\nx - 11 + 11 \u003e\u003d -1 + 11\n", "question": "Solve the inequality for x:\nx - 11 \u003e\u003d -1", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x \u003c 3", "explanation": "We want to get x by itself on one side of the inequality.\nUse addition to remove the constant.\n-2x + 12 - 12 \u003e 6 - 12\nNext, use the division to remove the coefficient\nRemember to switch the inequality because the coefficient is negative\n(-2x)/-2 \u003c -6/-2\n", "question": "Solve the inequality for x:\n-2x + 12 \u003e 6", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x \u003e 14", "explanation": "We want to get x by itself on one side of the inequality.\nUse addition to remove the constant.\n-13x + 1 - 1 \u003c -181 - 1\nNext, use the division to remove the coefficient\nRemember to switch the inequality because the coefficient is negative\n(-13x)/-13 \u003e -182/-13\n", "question": "Solve the inequality for x:\n-13x + 1 \u003c -181", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x \u003e\u003d 12", "explanation": "We want to get x by itself on one side of the inequality.\nUse addition to remove the constant.\n12x + 11 - 11 \u003e\u003d 155 - 11\nNext, use division to remove the coefficient.\n(12x)/12 \u003e\u003d 144/12\n", "question": "Solve the inequality for x:\n12x + 11 \u003e\u003d 155", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x \u003e 8", "explanation": "We want to get x by itself on one side of the inequality.\nUse addition to remove the constant.\nx - 8 + 8 \u003e 0 + 8\n", "question": "Solve the inequality for x:\nx - 8 \u003e 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x \u003c 8", "explanation": "We want to get x by itself on one side of the inequality.\nUse addition to remove the constant.\n9x + 10 - 10 \u003c 82 - 10\nNext, use division to remove the coefficient.\n(9x)/9 \u003c 72/9\n", "question": "Solve the inequality for x:\n9x + 10 \u003c 82", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x \u003c\u003d -7", "explanation": "We want to get x by itself on one side of the inequality.\nUse addition to remove the constant.\n10x + 11 - 11 \u003c\u003d -59 - 11\nNext, use division to remove the coefficient.\n(10x)/10 \u003c\u003d -70/10\n", "question": "Solve the inequality for x:\n10x + 11 \u003c\u003d -59", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x \u003c 8", "explanation": "We want to get x by itself on one side of the inequality.\nUse addition to remove the constant.\n4x + 10 - 10 \u003c 42 - 10\nNext, use division to remove the coefficient.\n(4x)/4 \u003c 32/4\n", "question": "Solve the inequality for x:\n4x + 10 \u003c 42", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x \u003c 6", "explanation": "We want to get x by itself on one side of the inequality.\nUse addition to remove the constant.\n11x + 1 - 1 \u003c 67 - 1\nNext, use division to remove the coefficient.\n(11x)/11 \u003c 66/11\n", "question": "Solve the inequality for x:\n11x + 1 \u003c 67", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x \u003e 13", "explanation": "We want to get x by itself on one side of the inequality.\nUse addition to remove the constant.\n-4x + 13 - 13 \u003c -39 - 13\nNext, use the division to remove the coefficient\nRemember to switch the inequality because the coefficient is negative\n(-4x)/-4 \u003e -52/-4\n", "question": "Solve the inequality for x:\n-4x + 13 \u003c -39", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x \u003c\u003d 4", "explanation": "We want to get x by itself on one side of the inequality.\nUse addition to remove the constant.\n-9x - 9 + 9 \u003e\u003d -45 + 9\nNext, use the division to remove the coefficient\nRemember to switch the inequality because the coefficient is negative\n(-9x)/-9 \u003c\u003d -36/-9\n", "question": "Solve the inequality for x:\n-9x - 9 \u003e\u003d -45", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x \u003c 10", "explanation": "We want to get x by itself on one side of the inequality.\nUse addition to remove the constant.\n-11x + 6 - 6 \u003e -104 - 6\nNext, use the division to remove the coefficient\nRemember to switch the inequality because the coefficient is negative\n(-11x)/-11 \u003c -110/-11\n", "question": "Solve the inequality for x:\n-11x + 6 \u003e -104", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x \u003e 15", "explanation": "We want to get x by itself on one side of the inequality.\nUse addition to remove the constant.\nx - 12 + 12 \u003e 3 + 12\n", "question": "Solve the inequality for x:\nx - 12 \u003e 3", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x \u003c\u003d -12", "explanation": "We want to get x by itself on one side of the inequality.\nUse addition to remove the constant.\n7x + 13 - 13 \u003c\u003d -71 - 13\nNext, use division to remove the coefficient.\n(7x)/7 \u003c\u003d -84/7\n", "question": "Solve the inequality for x:\n7x + 13 \u003c\u003d -71", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x \u003e\u003d 14", "explanation": "We want to get x by itself on one side of the inequality.\nUse addition to remove the constant.\n-4x + 7 - 7 \u003c\u003d -49 - 7\nNext, use the division to remove the coefficient\nRemember to switch the inequality because the coefficient is negative\n(-4x)/-4 \u003e\u003d -56/-4\n", "question": "Solve the inequality for x:\n-4x + 7 \u003c\u003d -49", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x \u003e\u003d 2", "explanation": "We want to get x by itself on one side of the inequality.\nUse addition to remove the constant.\n8x - 5 + 5 \u003e\u003d 11 + 5\nNext, use division to remove the coefficient.\n(8x)/8 \u003e\u003d 16/8\n", "question": "Solve the inequality for x:\n8x - 5 \u003e\u003d 11", "type": "text"}
]}